bemagenta.com 2018-08-16

# T-Mobile Magenta Gear - Privacy Policy

## THIS PRIVACY AND SECURITY STATEMENT DISCLOSES

The privacy practices and security measures in place for this website. We are committed to providing our customers with the safest and most pleasant online shopping experience possible.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to administer the site, track user movement and gather demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are directly linked to all order information as a measure to counter fraud.

## Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

## Links

This website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We recommend you read the privacy statements of each website that collects identifiable information.

## Security

This website takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected online. When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number, expiration date), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry-128 bit SSL.

## Children Under the Age of 13

We ask that children under 13 years of age not submit personal information on this site. The technology is not currently available to prevent children under 13 from submitting personal information without limiting the ability of other visitors. We suggest that parents supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers.

## WEBSITE SECURITY

By secure, we mean that this website uses the SSL protocol. Our web servers are capable of delivering 128-bit encryption. However, your browser, not the server, ultimately determines the exact level of encryption.

## SSL

Since online commerce sites deal with sensitive data, this website encrypts all transmissions containing personal data using the Secured Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. You may not be able to shop online if your browser does not support SSL or if you are accessing the Internet from behind a firewall that prohibits SSL transactions.

## SUPPORTED BROWSERS

This site requires JavaScript. [Supported Browsers.](http://www.mylogogear.com/shop/store/20130712007/browsers/index.html)

## COPYRIGHT

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button, icons, images, audio clips and software, is the property of HALO Branded Solutions or its content suppliers and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of HALO Branded Solutions and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. All software used on this site is the property of HALO Branded Solutions or its software suppliers and protected by U.S. and international copyright laws. The content and software on this site may be used as a shopping resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited
